advantagebridal.com 2018-06-30

# Advantage Bridal Security and Privacy Policy - Home

Advantage Bridal is committed to ensuring the privacy of our customers and utilizing all information only as needed, with utmost care and responsibility to our customers.  Please continue reading below for more detailed information about our privacy policy.

How We Collect Information 

Advantage Bridal uses a secure server (SSL) certified to encrypt all of your personal information. We use strong security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of your information once it is in our records.  We are tested daily by McAfee and Verisign also conducts frequent audits to ensure your safety while shopping online with us.

How We Use Information 

Our web site does not store the personal information we collect in order to process transactions for any purpose other than to fulfill your orders.  Your e-mail address, telephone number, and address from the order form are utilized solely to ship your orders to you.  We only use your contact information to reach you when it's necessary to communicate regarding your order. We never share your information with any other entity, and you will not end up on any mailing list by placing an order with us. You will have the opportunity to opt in to our mailing list if you desire, but that is the only means by which anyone is included. Financial information such as credit card numbers, credit card expiration dates, and your billing address which is collected is used only to bill you for the products and services you order from us, and is not stored.  Telephone numbers and e-mail addresses collected on any of our forms will only be used to contact you by mail or phone, or via automated e-mails in response to a form submission. 

Browser Cookies 

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers which are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your internet browser. They make it possible for us to store the contents of your shopping cart until you are ready to check out, and they recognize your browser when you visit our site again. By using cookies, we can personalize your return visits and save you time during checkout. In order to enjoy the benefits of being a registered user, your browser must be set to accept cookies.  In order to use our bridal registry, you must have cookies enabled.

Our Commitment to Excellence in Customer Service 

Advantage Bridal is committed to quality customer experience. We care a great deal about our customers, without whom we would not exist.  Although our store has been online since 1997, we think there is always room for improvement, and we love feedback from our customers, so that we can enhance your shopping experience. You can tell us what you think by sending us an e-mail or contacting our customer care department at 1-877-933-7467.  We encourage you to review the products you purchase from us so we can improve the shopping experience for all visitors to our site. If you send a testimonial to us, we may use it on our site, but will post your last name with your location unless we obtain your express permission.

Authorized Third Parties 

At times, Advantage Bridal utilizes third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. These providers may collect anonymous information about your visits to our web site and your interaction with our products.  They might also use information about your visits to this and other web sites to display relevent advertisements for goods and services to you. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is an industry standard technology used by most major web sites. No personally identifiable information about the user is collected or used in this process. You can also read more about online marketing practices and the technologies that support them by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative's](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) website. You may [ opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) of this data collection.  We also work with a third party provider to monitor certain pages of our web site for the purpose of reporting website traffic and statistics. Where authorized by us, this third party may use cookies and/or other monitoring technologies to compile statistics about our web site visitors. This information is always completely anonymous and no personally identifiable information is ever transferred.

Your Agreement 

By using our web site or purchasing a product from us, you agree to the collection and use of information as set forth in this privacy policy. We may from time to time update this policy, and we will post any changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect and how it is used.
